Guide to the Richard Kelly Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Richard Kelly papers
1909-1981
MS 1838
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
987.29
(434 boxes)
The papers include documentation for many of Richard Kelly's projects, including layouts and detailed working drawings, details of lighting fixtures, correspondence and architectural design drawings, and financial records. They also include correspondence with various institutions including universities and technical societies.
Kelly, Richard, 1910-1977
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Scott Kelly, 2005; Alex von Bidder, 2012; Addison and Scott Kelly, 2014.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged in three series: I. Project files, 1939-1977. II. Professional papers, 1909-1976. III. Personal papers, 1925-1981.
Biographical / Historical
Richard Kelly, architectural lighting designer, was born in Zanesville, Ohio, on September 22, 1910. After graduating from Columbia University in 1932, he opened an office in New York to design and sell architectural lighting. He enrolled in the architecture program at Yale University, where he also studied with theatrical lighting designer, Stanley McCandless, graduating with a B.F.A. in 1942. After working for several architectural offices, he opened his own lighting design firm in New York in or around 1947. Kelly developed a new vocabulary for architectural lighting, exploring the ways in which light affects mood, and identifying the concepts of focal glow, ambient luminescence, and the play of brilliants. During his career, Kelly worked with many noted architects, including Louis Kahn, Ludwig Mies van der Rohe, Harrison and Abramovitz, Eero Saarinen, I. M. Pei, and Philip Johnson. Among his notable projects are: the Seagram Building and Lincoln Center in New York, the Kimbell Art Museum in Fort Worth, Texas, and the Yale Center for British Art in New Haven, Connecticut. In addition to his own practice, Kelly lectured on lighting design at Yale University, Harvard University, Cooper Union, Columbia, and other architectural schools and organizations. He died in 1977.
Scope and Contents
The papers include documentation for many of Richard Kelly's projects, including layouts and detailed working drawings, details of lighting fixtures, correspondence and architectural design drawings, and financial records. They also include correspondence with various institutions, including universities and technical societies, as well as some personal papers and student work.
Other Finding Aids
For a list of projects and the boxes in which project materials are located, please consult the Project Index.
Lighting, Architectural and decorative; Kelly, Richard, 1910-1977; Four Seasons (Restaurant); Kimbell Art Museum; Seagram Building (New York, N.Y.); Yale Center for British Art
- Project files, 1939-1977; Series I
  Other Finding Aids
  For a list of projects and the boxes in which project materials are located, please consult the Project Index.
  - 10 East 40th Street Lobby (See also: Lessman, Jac Office)
    Scope and Contents
    Job location: New York, NY
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 1)
  - 81st Street and East River Drive, 1951
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 1)
  - 117 East 57th Street (See also: The Galleria)
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 1)
    - Drawings (Box 1, Box 382)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 1)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 1)
  - 200 Madison Avenue, 1965
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 1)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 1)
  - 230 Peachtree Building, 1951
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 1, Box 404)
    - Drawings (Box 178, Box 303, Box 317)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 404)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 178, Box 303)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 303, Box 317, Box 404)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 178, Box 303)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 178, Box 303, Box 317)
    - Drawings: As-Built/Record Set (Box 178)
  - 445 Park Avenue, 1965
    Job location: Atlanta, GA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 1)
  - 500 North Michigan Avenue, 1947
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 1)
    - Drawings (Box 1)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 1)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 1)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 1)
  - 1789 Restaurant, 1967
    Job location: Chicago, IL
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 1)
    - Drawings (Box 234)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 1, Box 234)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 234)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 1)
    - Photographs (Box 1)
  - Adler and Adler, 1962
    Job location: Georgetown, Washington, D.C.
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 1)
    - Drawings (Box 1)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 1)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 1)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 1)
  - Air India Ticket Office, 1951
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 1)
    - Drawings (Box 1)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 1)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 1)
  - American Academy of Music
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 1)
  - American Fletcher National Bank
    Job location: Philadelphia, PA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 1)
  - American Home Magazine
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 1)
  - American President Lines
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 1)
    - Drawings (Box 1)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 1)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 1)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 1)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 1)
  - Anemostat Corporation of America, 1955
    Job location: San Francisco, CA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 1)
    - Drawings (Box 1)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 1)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 1)
    - Photographs (Box 1)
  - Angell Residence
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 1)
    - Drawings (Box 1)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 1)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 1)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 1)
  - Ansul Company
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 1)
  - Apartment on Mount Washington, 1966
    Job location: Wisconsin
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 1)
  - Architect's Collaborative, 1962
    Job location: Pittsburgh, PA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 1)
    - Drawings (Box 1)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 1)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 1)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 1)
  - Architectural League of New York
    Job location: Cambridge, MA
    Collaborator: Philip Johnson
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 1)
  - Arden, Elizabeth Apartment, 1959
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 1)
  - Art Institute of Zanesville, 1956
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 1)
    - Drawings (Box 1)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 1)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 1)
    - Photographs (Box 1)
  - Art Metal Company
    Job location: Zanesville, OH
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 1)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 1)
  - Arthur, Jean, 1952
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 1)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 1)
    - Photographs (Box 1)
  - Arts Club of Chicago
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 1)
    - Drawings (Box 1)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 1)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 1)
  - Ashley-Kent, Ltd., 1951
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 2)
    - Drawings (Box 2)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 2)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 2)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 2)
  - Asia House, 1950
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 2)
    - Drawings (Box 2)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 2)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 2)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 2)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 2)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 2)
  - Asian Society Building, 1959
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 2)
    - Drawings (Box 2)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 2)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 2)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 2)
  - Athens Airport, 1957
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 2)
  - Atlanta Airport, 1959
    Job location: Athens, Greece
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 2)
    - Drawings (Box 2)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 2)
  - Atrium Club, Galleria Building
    - Drawings (Box 120)
  - Ault, Lee Residence
    Job location: New Canaan, NY
    Collaborator: Eliot Noyes
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 2)
    - Drawings (Box 2)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 2)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 2)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 2, Box 404)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 2)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 2)
    - Photographs (Box 2)
  - Australia Square Tower Building, 1952
    Job location: Sydney, Australia
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 2)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 2)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 301)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 301)
    - Photographs (Box 2)
  - Automative Workers of America, 1965
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 2)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 2)
    - Photographs (Box 25)
  - Ayer & Son
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 2)
    - Drawings (Box 2)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 2)
  - Bacon Residence, 1958
    Job location: Idlewild, NY
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 2)
    - Drawings (Box 2)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 2)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 2)
  - Balitmore Museum, 1952
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 2)
    - Drawings (Box 2)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 2)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 2)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 2)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 2)
    - Photographs (Box 2)
  - Banghart, Kenneth, 1961
    Job location: Baltimore, MD
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 2)
    - Photographs (Box 2)
  - Bankers Trust Company, 1960
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 3, Box 404)
    - Drawings (Box 3, Box 174, Box 180, Box 230, Box 238, Box 300)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 3, Box 181, Box 300)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 3, Box 181, Box 230, Box 300)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 3, Box 180–181, Box 238, Box 403)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 3, Box 180–181, Box 230, Box 238, Box 300, Box 402)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 3, Box 180, Box 300, Box 403)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 3)
    - Drawings: As-Built/Record Set (Box 3)
  - Bankers Trust Company, Lincoln Square Branch, 1963
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 3)
    - Drawings (Box 3)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 3)
  - Barber Residence, 1960
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 4)
    - Drawings (Box 4)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 4, Box 404)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 4)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 4)
    - Drawings: As-Built/Record Set (Box 4)
  - Barbizon Plaza Hotel, 1953
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 4)
    - Drawings (Box 4)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 404)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 4)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 4, Box 399)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 4)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 4)
    - Drawings: As-Built/Record Set (Box 4)
    - Photographs (Box 4, Box 404)
  - Barclay Hotel, 1954
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 4)
    - Drawings (Box 4, Box 286)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 4)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 4)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 4, Box 286)
    - Photographs (Box 4)
  - Bassevitch Residence, 1956
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 4)
    - Drawings (Box 4)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 4)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 4)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 4, Box 404)
  - Beck, Henry L. Residence, 1950
    Job location: West Hartford, CT
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 4)
    - Drawings (Box 4, Box 307)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 4)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 4)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 4)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 4, Box 307)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 4, Box 307)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 307)
  - Bell Telephone Laboratories (See Also: Western Electric Company Incorporated), 1962
    Job location: Dallas, TX Collaborator: Eero Saarinen
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 4)
    - Drawings (Box 4, Box 205)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 4)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 4, Box 205)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 4, Box 205)
    - Photographs (Box 4)
  - Bellevue Stratford Hotel, 1960
    Job location: Holmdel, NJ
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 5)
    - Drawings (Box 5)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 5)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 5)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 5)
  - Bender and Hamburger Inc., 1956
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 5)
    - Drawings (Box 5)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 5)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 5)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 5)
    - Photographs (Box 5)
  - Berking Residence, 1952
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 5)
    - Drawings (Box 5)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 5)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 5)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 5)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 5)
    - Drawings: As-Built/Record Set (Box 5)
  - Berman, Eugene, 1955
    Job location: Rye, NY
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 5)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 5)
  - Bernhard House, 1954
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 5)
    - Drawings: As-Built/Record Set (Box 5)
    - Photographs (Box 5)
  - Beverly Hills Club, 1959
    Job location: Newport, KT
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 5)
    - Drawings (Box 5)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 5)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 5)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 5)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 5)
    - Photographs (Box 5)
  - Bielefeld Museum, 1956
    Job location: Bielefeld, Germany
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 5)
  - Blades, Gay, 1965
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 5)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 5)
  - B'nai B'rith Building, 1954
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 5)
    - Drawings (Box 5)
  - Boissonnas Residence, 1957
    Job location: Cap Benat, France
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 5)
    - Drawings (Box 5)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 5)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 5)
  - Boisonnas Residence, 1955
    Job location: New Canaan, CT
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 5)
    - Drawings (Box 5)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 5)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 5)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 5)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 5)
  - Bonwit Teller Inc., 1947
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 5)
    - Drawings (Box 5)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 5)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 5)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 5)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 5)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 6)
    - Photographs (Box 6)
  - Brandeis University, 1947
    Job location: Boston, MA Collaborator: Eero Saarinen
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 6)
    - Drawings (Box 6)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 6)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 6, Box 382)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 6, Box 382)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 6, Box 382)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 6)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 6)
  - Bridges Art Gallery, 1952
    Job location: Waltham, MA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 6)
    - Drawings (Box 6, Box 131)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 131)
  - British Art Center (See: Paul Mellon Center for British Art)
  - British Overseas Airways Corporation (B.O.A.C), 1958
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 6)
    - Drawings (Box 6)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 6)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 6)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 6)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 6)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 6)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 6)
    - Drawings: As-Built/Record Set (Box 6)
  - Bromeliad Society of America, 1970
    Job location: New Haven, CT
    Collaborator: Louis Kahn
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 6)
    - Drawings (Box 6)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 6)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 6)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 6)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 6)
    - Drawings: As-Built/Record Set (Box 6)
  - Brookline Country Club, 1950-1959
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 6)
    - Drawings (Box 6)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 6)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 6)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 6)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 6)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 6)
    - Drawings: As-Built/Record Set (Box 6)
  - Brooklyn Museum, 1959
    Job location: Brookline, MA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 7)
    - Drawings (Box 7)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 7)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 7)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 7)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 7)
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - Brown, Anne S. K. Library, 1967
    Job location: Brooklyn, NY
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 7)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 7)
  - Brown,David residence
    Job location: Chapel Hill, NC
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 404)
  - Brown, Reese F., 1958
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 7)
  - Brown University, 1956
    Job location: Providence, RI
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 7)
    - Drawings (Box 7)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 7)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 7)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 7)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 7)
    - Drawings: As-Built/Record Set (Box 7)
  - Brown Univsersity: S.K. Brown Library, 1956
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 7)
    - Drawings (Box 7)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 7)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 7)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 7)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 7)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 7)
  - Brussels Restaurant, 1958
    Collaborator: James E. Casale
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 7)
    - Drawings (Box 7)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 7)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 7)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 7)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 7)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 7)
    - Drawings: As-Built/Record Set (Box 7)
  - Buckeye Federal Savings and Loan Association, 1963
    Job location: Columbus, OH
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 7)
    - Drawings (Box 7, Box 175)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 7, Box 175)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 7, Box 175)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 175)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 7, Box 175)
  - Budd Company, 1965
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 7)
    - Drawings (Box 7, Box 202)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 7)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 7, Box 202)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 7)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 7)
    - Drawings: As-Built/Record Set (Box 7)
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - Burden, William Apartment, 1954
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 7)
    - Drawings (Box 7)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 7, Box 404)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 7, Box 382, Box 404)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 7, Box 404)
  - Burden William House, 1956
    Job location: Mt. Kisco, NY
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 7)
    - Drawings (Box 7)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 7)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 7)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 7)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 7, Box 382)
  - Burden, William House, 1959
    Job location: Northeast Harbor, ME
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 7)
    - Drawings (Box 7)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 7)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 7)
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - Burlington Industries, Inc., 1969
    Job location: Greensboro, NC
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 7)
    - Drawings (Box 7)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 7)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 7)
  - Cagen Residence, 1951
    Job location: Hampstead, Long Island, NY
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 8)
  - Calhoun Residence, 1947
    Job location: Connecticut
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 8)
    - Drawings (Box 8)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 8)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 8)
    - Photographs (Box 8)
  - California Federal Savings and Loan Association, 1962
    Job location: Los Angeles, CA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 8)
    - Drawings (Box 8, Box 306)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 8)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 8, Box 306)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 8, Box 306)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 306)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 306)
    - Material Samples (Box 8)
  - Callery, Mary
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 8)
    - Drawings (Box 8)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 8)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 8)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 8)
    - Photographs (Box 8)
  - Campanile, 1947
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 8)
    - Drawings (Box 8)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 8)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 8)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 8)
    - Drawings: As-Built/Record Set (Box 8)
  - Canal Commercial Trust and Savings Bank, 1949
    Job location: New Orleans, LA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 8, Box 382)
    - Drawings (Box 8)
    - Drawings: Landscape (Box 8)
    - Drawings: As-Built/Record Set (Box 8)
    - Photographs (Box 8)
  - Caneel Bay Plantation, Inc., 1960
    Job location: St. John, Virgin Islands
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 8)
    - Drawings (Box 8)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 8)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 8)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 8)
  - Capitol Building, 1956
    Job location: Washington, D.C.
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 8)
    - Photographs (Box 8)
  - Capitol Car Distributors, Ltd., 1964
    Job location: Prince Georges County, MD
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 8)
    - Drawings (Box 8)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 8)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 8)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 8)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 8)
    - Working Drawings: Mechanical/Electrical/Plumbing (Box 8)
  - Carnegie Hall, 1960
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 8)
    - Drawings (Box 8)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 8)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 8)
    - Working Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 8)
    - Material Samples (Box 8)
  - Carnegie Study of the Arts
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 8)
  - Carter, Hawley, & Hale, 1959
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 8, Box 404)
  - Carter Museum of Western Art, 1961
    Job location: Fort Worth, TX
    - Manuscript Materials (Box 8)
    - Drawings (Box 8, Box 304)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 8)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 8)
    - Drawings: Lighting (Box 8, Box 304)